

Objective

To start a new journey after receiving basic theories in university the third-year internship position will be the gained new knowledge as well as work in a professional environment. With the knowledge of three years of study in institute and life experiences, I will bring to the business the most professional quality of work and hope to hone my skills for future life development.

Education

VNUK Institute for Research and Executive Education [Oct 2020 - Dec 2022]

Junior Student

Major: Computure Science and Engineering

Work experience

Hekate, 18 Phan Thanh Tai, Da Nang, Vietnam [Jan 2020 - Apr 2020]

First-year trainee

Recognition and Gains:

- -Learning how to approaching to new programing language
- -Solving difficult problem that happen on the job
- -Acquire knowledge of working processes in a company environment

Green Global, Da Nang, Vietnam [Apr 2023 - Aug 2023]

Reactis intern

Recognition and Gains:

- -Learning how to using API
- -Apply some libaries related to Reactjs

Activities

- JunctionX Hanoi 2021 [December, 2020]

Participant

- -Generate ideas in short time
- -Improve teamwork skill
- -Challenge myself to step out of my comfort zone

Contact information

(+84) 983 126 926 hieu.le200220@vnuk.edu.vn Da Nang , Vietnam

Skills

- -Team work: Work with friends and mentor in our team in JuntionX Hanoi 2021 competition
- -English: Reading and researching documents about major and improve my English skills.
- -Individual work: Do independent presentation exercises at school.

Certifications

IELTS CERTIFICATE WITH SCORE 5.5 ISSUED BY IDP VIETNAM

[MAY 2020]